http://www.saskflax.com/privacy.php

Privacy & Legal
Read our Privacy Policy and Legal Disclaimer below.
Privacy
Your privacy is important to the Saskatchewan Flax Development Commission. This statement discloses the privacy practices of the SaskFlax website, www.saskflax.com. The privacy policy of this website adheres to the latest privacy legislation enacted by the Government of Canada. Your privacy and personal information is protected by the Privacy Act and the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA).
We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update or modify our privacy policy (in accordance with federal legislation) by posting such change, update or modification on our website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on our website, www.saskflax.com.
If you have questions about our privacy policy contact us at 306-664-1901.
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through our website and read the information contained on the Web pages, we may gather certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally.
WE DO NOT DISCLOSE ANY NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU WITH ANYONE FOR ANY PURPOSE THAT IS NOT SPECIFICALLY PERMITTED BY LAW.
We may automatically gather the Internet domain (for example, 'yourcompany.com' if you use a private Internet access account, or 'schoolname.edu' if you connect from a university's domain), IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website, and the date and time you access our website and the pages you visit.
We may collect nonpublic personal information from you when you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information to us though our Website. We may collect information that we secure from our files and from our affiliates. We may collect information that we receive from consumer reporting agencies. We may collect information that we receive from others involved in your transactions, such as real estate agents or lenders. We limit use of such information to the purposes for which the information was provided.
However, we reserve the right to use such information for marketing/product development research and other similar purposes and/or to contact you regarding additional services or products that you may find useful.
If you send an electronic mail (email) message that includes personally identifiable information, for example, in an email message containing an inquiry, we will use that information to respond to your inquiry. Remember that email is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication is very sensitive, or includes information such as your bank account, charge card, or social insurance number, you should not send it electronically unless it is encrypted or our website indicates the particular site is secure.
Our employees may view information that you provide us in order to perform their jobs and service you. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We do not share nonpublic personal information to third parties who are not affiliated with us, unless the law allows us to do so.
Our website may contain links to other websites that are provided and maintained exclusively by third parties. Websites provided and maintained by third parties are not subject to this privacy policy. Please review the privacy policies on those websites to understand their personal information handling practices. We make no representations concerning the privacy policies of these third party websites.
Legal Disclaimer
The information and links contained on this website are being provided by the Saskatchewan Flax Development Commission for general information purposes only. This website may include links to third party websites over which SaskFlax has no control. SaskFlax makes no representations as to the accuracy or any other aspect of the information contained in such third party websites.
Furthermore, SaskFlax makes no representations about the suitability, reliability, availability, timeliness, and accuracy of the information contained on this website for any purpose. The information contained on this website is provided 'as is' without warranty of any kind.
The Saskatchewan Flax Development Commission hereby disclaims all warranties and conditions with regard to this website, including all implied warranties and conditions or merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title and non-infringement.
In no event shall SaskFlax be liable for any direct, indirect, punitive, incidental, special, consequential damages or any damages whatsoever arising out of or in any way connected with the use or performance of this website.
©
SASKATCHEWAN FLAX DEVELOPMENT COMMISSION
SITE MAP / PRIVACY POLICY
The Flax Industry
Industry Overview
Reconstituted Flaxseed
Policy Issues
Statistics & Trends
